Natalia Rudnicki, QA Engineer

Cologne, Germany • +49 160 98930471 • natalia.v.rudnicki@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/nataliarudnicki

SUMMARY

QA Engineer with more than two years of experience in software testing and quality assurance of web and mobile applications in agile environment and deep understanding of software development principles and the QA role in this process.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Open Reply GmbH, Cologne, Germany, Nov 2022 – Present, QA Engineer

- Created testing documentation to ensure quality control and detect bugs by increasing over 35% efficiency rate.
- Improved testing processes which led to release testing 80% bug free.
- Maintained high quality standards of 8 mobile and 2 web applications daily by performing backend and frontend testing.

Utest.com, remote, March 2021 – Nov 2022, QA Engineer

- Performed regression, smoke, API, end-to-end, integration testing which improved the quality of the product by 50%.
- Worked with the development team of 10 people to explore edge cases to ensure adequate test coverage.
- Developed test plans and test cases to cover business use cases resulting in an increased efficiency rate of over 25%.

DLA Piper Rus Limited, Moscow, Russia, Feb 2010 – Jan 2021, Executive Assistant

- Implemented processes using the company's finance software improving the efficiency by 30%.
- Collaborated with executive team members to determine and prioritize business strategies leading to 15% of profit increase.
- Reviewed, interpreted and analysed data to assist the executive leadership in their decision making.

EDUCATION

- Functional Testing Course, Nov 2022 Jun 2023
- Udemy, Tester from Scratch, 2022
- Udemy, The Complete 2022 Testing Software Bootcamp, 2022
- QA Mentor University, **Professional Training in Software Quality Assurance and Testing**, 2021
- Moscow State Institute of International Relations (MGIMO), 2013 2016, Master of Laws
- Moscow State Linguistic University (MGLU), 2004 2009, Specialist Degree in Linguistics

CERTIFICATIONS

ISTQB® Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL), 2022

SKILLS & OTHER

Skills: Jira, Bugzilla, Confluence, Qase, TestRail, Postman, Charles, Android Studio, BrowserStack, GitHub, SQL, MongoDB, JSON, HTML

Languages: English (full working proficiency), German (limited working proficiency (B2)), Russian (native)